<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brisca3.0</string>

    <string name="titulo">Brisca3.0</string>
    <string name="boton1">New game</string>
    <string name="boton2">Join game</string>
    <string name="boton3">Statistics</string>
    <string name="boton4">Instructions</string>
    <string name="boton5">Rules</string>
    <string name="boton6">Preferences</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nombrePartida">Game Name</string>

    <!--ReglasBrisca-->
    <string name="title_activity_reglas_brisca">Briscas Rules</string>
    <string name="reglas_descripcion">Description</string>
    <string name="reglas_descripcion_text">It is a game of Spanish deck of 40 cards. The Brisca
        belongs to the large family of card games Tute, games in question
        go getting tricks , with a dominant pole or trump. Brisca in a variable number of players
        faces arranged around the table. The recommended amount of players is 2 or 4 pairs.
    </string>

    <string name="reglas_objetivo">Game Objetives</string>
    <string name="reglas_objetivo_text">The general objective of the game is to win the number of points / hands
        initially agreed before the other players, and the specific goal to win each of those hands is
        score as many points as possible with the cards won in each trick. We will have to try to take
        a large number of tricks but tricks with cards from the highest score possible .
    </string>

    <string name="reglas_juego">Game Development</string>
    <string name="reglas_juego1">The Match Start</string>
    <string name="reglas_juego1_text">It is cast lots to see who is the dealer for the first time and who hand
        (Which is placed to the right of the dealer).
        In each hand the dealer will give cut the deck to the player on his left,
        and then will distribute the cards to each player one by one and left to right.
        When you have finished dealing cards that correspond to each player in that particular hand,
        will raise the next visible leaving on deck throughout the hand, that letter will be the paint,
        which mark the victory in that hand.
        Each hand has several advantages, as many as the number obtained by dividing the number of letters
        of the deck between the players involved. In short, an asset is the set of cards (one for each player)
        throwing on the table players in their respective turn. Each time you complete an asset will be a player who wins,
        it takes.
    </string>
    <string name="reglas_juego2">Play the Cards</string>
    <string name="reglas_juego2_text">The hand that goes to the center of the mat cast one of his letters ( which he likes )
        and the other , from left to right, they throw more each, which they want, without limitations or
        obligations of any kind regarding which take .
    </string>
    <string name="reglas_juego3">Pick up the tricks</string>
    <string name="reglas_juego3_text">The trick is obtained by the player who had thrown the highest card of the trump suit,
        and if there is no trumps on the table, the highest card of the suit led.
        The hierarchy between cards of the same suit is as follows, from highest to lowest: Ace, Three, King, Knight, Jack, seven,
        six, five, four, two.
        In successive assets within the same hand, the player who has taken the last trick is to start
        launching the 1st letter of the next trick.
        Before launching the cards to play a new trick again, all players take a card off the deck,
        Starting for which he won the previous trick, so you always have three cards in hand. Logically,
        As you complete the game in one hand, the cards in the deck will end and there will come a time when there will be card drawing:
        in the last three tricks will be played only with the cards you have in hand (two in the penultimate and the last).
        When the cards in the deck are finished, the last player takes the letter states the trump suit.
    </string>
    <string name="reglas_juego4">Scoring the tricks</string>
    <string name="reglas_juego4_text">Once you have completed all the tricks of a hand,
        we will proceed to count the points earned by each player in the hand.
        For these purposes the value of each letter is as follows : Ace (11 points ) , Three ( 10 points), Rey (4 points )
        Horse ( 3 points) and Sota ( 2 points). The remaining cards have no scoring value.
        The total number of points you add the card deck is 120 .
        The player with most points in one hand, which will win.
        In case of a tie on points between two or more players will be allocated as won hands with each of them .
    </string>
    <string name="reglas_juego5">Changing Cards</string>
    <string name="reglas_juego5_text">When a player has in his hand during the game seven of trumps ,
        you can change it to the letter if it were a paint -value card (Ace, Three , Rey, Caballo or Sota ) .
        This change can be made right after winning one trick and before proceeding to steal the corresponding card from the deck .
        This same change , and the same rules and limitations, players may do so if they had in their possession two and
        would change from the letter to mark the victory if it were a letter without value ( Four, Five, Six or Seven ) .
    </string>
    <string name="reglas_final">End of the Game</string>
    <string name="reglas_final_text">The game ends when one player reaches the number of winning hands
        previously agreed , and if more than one simultaneously reached , the game ends when
        this tie is broken in successive hands played to this end.
    </string>

    <!--InstruccionesBrisca-->
    <string name="title_activity_instrucciones_brisca">Game Instructions</string>

    <string name="instrucciones_1">Instructions</string>

    <!--Crear nueva partida-->
    <string name="title_activity_crear_nueva_partida">Create new game</string>
    <string name="mens_nombre_partida">Write the name of the game</string>

    <!--Conectar-->
    <string name="conect_enviar">Send</string>

    <!--Partida-->
    <string name="partida_titulo">Game</string>
    <string name="partida_jugador1">Player 1</string>
    <string name="partida_jugador2">Player 2</string>
    <string name="partida_mensajes">Mensages</string>
    <string name="partida_carta3j2">Card 3 of player 2</string>
    <string name="partida_carta2j2">Card 2 del player 2</string>
    <string name="partida_carta1j2">Card 1 del player 2</string>
    <string name="partida_carta3j1">Card 3 del player 1</string>
    <string name="partida_carta2j1">Card 2 del player 1</string>
    <string name="partida_carta1j1">Card 1 del player 1</string>
    <string name="partida_mazo">Deck of cards</string>
    <string name="partida_pinta">Carta que pinta</string>
    <string name="partida_espacio1">Space for player 1 place his card</string>
    <string name="partida_espacio2">Space for player 2 place his card</string>

    <!--Preferencias-->
    <string name="pref_categoria1_title">Player info</string>
    <string name="pref_categoria2_title">Game info</string>
    <string name="pref_nombreusuario">Player name</string>
    <string name="pref_nombreusuario_summary">Change player name</string>
    <string name="pref_nombreusuario_dialog">Name</string>
    <string name="pref_idioma_title">Lenguage</string>
    <string name="pref_idioma_summary">Game lenguage(not implemented jet)</string>
    <string name="pref_idioma_dialog">Select lenguage</string>
</resources>




